Dini , you gotta help me find a new place .
My nosy neighbors are getting worse .
They 're saying I come home late because I 'm a hooker .
Does that bother you ?
No . But I 'm not a hooker .
Maybe it 's easier being a hooker . You sleep with them , then they pay you .
It wouldn 't be that easy .
You have to put on makeup , or your client may be rough or too big .
- You have to know how to pick them . - But how ?
How would I know if a client is too rough or too big before ?
You need to check first before agreeing .
If his dick wasn 't aroused , how would you know it would be too big ?
I would know . You wouldn 't because you 're a clueless virgin .
Hang on , a car is coming .
You didn 't put me on speaker ?
- The boss finds out , you 'll be in trouble . - Done .
- Aren 't you using up all your phone data ? - I don 't care . It 's creepy in here .
Who 's on shift with you ?
Mr. Chondro . But he left for the office . I don 't know why he hasn 't come back yet .
They 're closing this toll booth soon . Not many cars come through this gate .
Soon no one will be assigned to any gate .
It 's ridiculous they 're replacing everybody with machines .
Nobody 'll have a job in the future .
That 's why we need to start our clothing store soon .
Well , I won 't miss this . I won 't have to deal with so many weird people .
Like the guy in the old car that has been stalking me for weeks .
We 've talked about this .
Maybe he 's just coming home from work every day .
Dini , he drove by here several times in one night . Isn 't that weird ?
And he looks at me as if he 's going to eat me alive .
What are you , a newbie ? I already told you ,
don 't ever look the drivers in their eyes . Just look at their hands .
His hands were gross . Dirty fingernails and all .
Maybe he 's a gravedigger .
You 're not helping . It 's easy for you because you 're not alone .
Who is stationed with you ?
I 'm with Wahyu , and now he steals a glance at me .
He 's been driving me home these past three days .
Is Wahyu really into second-hand items like you ?
Hey . Can 't you listen to other songs ?
It 's so last century . It sounds creepy .
No . My radio 's stuck in AM . The FM mode is not working .
Shit .
What 's wrong ?
That old car is here again .
Hello ?
Maya ?
He 's still here .
Really ? What is he doing ?
I have no idea . He 's staring at me .
I 'm calling the office .
He 's finally gone . Thank you , sir !
Shit , my heart almost stopped .
Dini , that old car is still here .
And the driver is walking towards me ! What should I do ?
Dini ?
- Okay , stay calm . I 'm calling the office . - Dini ...
Can anyone send someone to Bukit Selatan 1 gate now ?
Someone is harassing an officer .
- Now , please ! - Dini !
Okay . Just stay calm .
Lock the door ! Close the window !
Find any object that is near you !
What do you mean ?
A metal stick , a rock , anything that you can use as a weapon .
There 's nothing here . I 'm dead meat !
Security guards are coming !
Rahayu is your name , right ?
No , my name 's Maya . Can 't you read the name on the sign ?
Is that your real name ?
Yes .
Hey ! Don 't mess with her ! Go away !
Are you from Harjosari Village in Mandiraja ?
What do you want ?
Is your father 's name Ki Donowongso ?
Maya .
Is he gone yet ? He 's already gone ...
If help doesn 't come soon , just get out of there .
Leave your post !
Okay .
Hey , has someone been sent to help her ?
Dini , he 's coming back with a weapon !
What weapon ?
Maya !
- Help ! Oh no ... - Maya !
Anyone , help !
Hey !
Drop your weapon !
We ...
just don 't want what your family left behind .
Please take it away ...
- Ma 'am , I have new stuff . - Not now .
Then pay for the shirt you bought last week .
- The second installment is due . - I can 't pay you right now .
But you have lots of customers !
Exactly . I 'm busy now .
Come on . Just get your purse and give me my money .
Do you want a new bra ?
We should 've checked first whether this market was good for business .
Just let it go .
We got duped because the rent is cheap .
We 'll sell these online .
These crappy fakes ?
That 's why we 'll sell it online .
So the customers can 't tell the difference .
Even I wouldn 't wear one of these .
I 'd rather wear a plastic bag or a rice sack .
Sorry I dragged you into this . We used up all your money .
Forget it . It 's not like you put a gun to my head . I wanted to join too .
I 'm going away for a week or so .
Where to ?
Who are they ?
After the attack , I dug into my late aunt 's stuff .
I found this photo .
I think they 're my parents .
You " think " ?
Well , I never saw photos of them before .
And I was too young to remember them .
KI DONOWONGSO , NYAI SHINTA RAHAYU AGE 5 YEARS OLD
" Rahayu " ?
So the psychopath was right ?
I do remember my aunt called me Rahayu when I was young .
Then she started calling me Maya . I don 't know why .
So what ?
Take a closer look .
You were short when you were little ?
You mean , the house ?
This very big house
is the key to solving our problems . My family 's house .
But we don 't even know where it is .
The psycho mentioned the name of the village .
Harjosari Village , Mandiraja . I looked it up .
This could be our chance to start a new life .
I 'm going with you .
No , you can 't .
Maya , you are my best friend . No way I will let you go alone .
And if you turn out to be rich , you can 't leave me behind .
What about our kiosk ?
" Screw it ! Nobody comes buying anyway . "
Hey ! You can 't smoke in there !
You can 't be in here , pervert ! This is the ladies ' room !
- Shut up ! Get the hell out of here ! - I 'm just telling you .
What happened ?
It 's the wound .
How come it still looks fresh ?
I don 't know . I just need some antiseptic .
There 's blood and I know it 's not that time of the month for you .
Stay here , I 'll get you some antiseptic .
Dini ?
You haven 't gone home ?
Not yet .
Dini ?
Hey .
People are getting lazier these days .
They turn the lights off early and lock the doors .
The pharmacy is closed .
No medicine for you , then .
Come on .
HAVE A NICE TRIP
What are you reading ?
Business planning .
What business ?
Any business . So I will know my way around if we 're to start another .
Besides , if I don 't read , I 'll just go to the toilet all the time .
Turn off your light . The guy behind us is annoyed .
Goddamn hillbilly .
How long until we get there ?
The driver said six hours .
See , now I have to pee .
Use this blanket .
You 're not going to need it ?
I don 't feel cold . Just go to sleep .
I 'll wake you up when we reach your parents ' village .
I wasn 't bothered by you nor your friend .
I sometimes cough so the spirits on this bus won 't bother the passengers .
" Spirits " ?
That 's right . There are spirits on this bus .
They don 't know where to go .
Don 't think I 'm crazy .
I 'm a university lecturer .
A lecturer ? What do you teach ?
Russian literature .
I know it 's not much use in this country .
But I love the Russian language .
Well , I love all languages .
You know Javanese ?
Why would I study foreign languages if I don 't know my own ?
Do you know what this says ?
This is very ancient Javanese .
It 's a spell so that the carrier won 't be bothered by evil spirits .
So this is like an amulet ?
Yes . But this was made by an evil person .
Where did you get this picture ?
From the Internet .
What 's on your mind ?
Nothing .
You 're thinking about your parents ?
You seriously don 't know anything about them ?
All my life , I lived with my aunt . She wasn 't much of a talker .
If I asked her about my parents , she wouldn 't say much .
Parents are overrated .
I 've lived with my parents all my life .
It didn 't do me any good . Didn 't make me happier .
But at least you know them .
That 's true . Especially if your parents may have left you with a fortune .
But we really have to be careful .
That 's why we 're going there just to check things out .
If I do have some sort of inheritance , we 'll come back with a lawyer .
Lawyer ? How fancy .
Dini , thank you for coming with me .
Don 't mention it .
Just pray we won 't have to stay in a place with cockroaches .
- Shit ! - What 's wrong ?
I saw three little girls standing by the side of the road earlier .
Impossible . It 's 1 : 00 a.m. All children are sleeping .
I swear to God !
How long did you say before we get there ?
Five hours .
Dini ...
Sir , have you heard of Harjosari Village ?
- Harjosari ? - Yes .
Never heard of it , miss .
Where did you look the place up ? Google ?
I tried but couldn 't find it .
So I checked with the local government . It 's under their territory .
Well nobody ever heard of it !
We 've only asked one person .
Maya !
Sir , have you heard of Harjosari Village ?
Of course .
Can you take us there ?
No .
Why ?
It 's too far .
How much do you want ?
A hundred thousand rupiahs .
Okay .
For each of you .
Where are you from , " Bloodsuckers Village " ?
I 'm from " Handsome and Rich Village . "
Wait until my horse finishes his lunch .
When did you last feed him ? Last month ?
Last year .
Hi , sweetie .
Why do you want to go to Harjosari ?
We 're university students , and we 're doing research .
In Harjosari ? Research on what ? Population census ?
Why are you laughing ?
There 's nothing in Harjosari . It 's a secluded village .
That 's why . We 're doing research on secluded villages .
I see .
What do you know about the village ?
Not much .
I know about the village because I recently took their village elder home .
The village elder is a puppet master . He was in my town for a performance .
What 's his name ?
Ki Saptadi .
He 's quite well-known .
Why don 't they build a proper road to the village ?
I heard that the village people didn 't want to .
Why ?
I don 't know .
Dini , please take off those sunglasses .
But it 's too sunny .
What 's your plan ?
Miss , where do you want me to drop you off ?
Just drop us off at Ki Saptadi 's , the village elder 's house .
Are you sure ?
Okay .
Well , I don 't think we can find a hotel here .
Are we staying the night in this village ?
I don 't know .
- What do you mean you don 't know ? - Depends on the situation .
We don 't even know if my house still exists .
I didn 't ask you to come with me .
Just go home if you want to .
The house is huge .
Do you know whose house that is ?
I don 't know .
I asked Ki Saptadi when we passed the house , but he didn 't say anything .
What a waste , right ? A house that big sitting empty .
It 's better to give it to me .
Giddyap !
All right .
Do you want me to wait for you ?
No , but thanks a lot .
If you want me to pick you up , call my number .
Thank you .
Let 's go , gorgeous .
We need to come up with a new story .
There 's no way we can say we 're students .
- Why not ? - Well ...
What if he asks too many questions about the university ?
I don 't know anything . Do you ?
Just don 't say we 're students .
- What then ? - Let me think .
Who are you looking for ?
We are university students , ma 'am . Can we meet Ki Saptadi ?
What for ?
We are writing a book on puppet masters .
We heard Ki Saptadi is a famous puppet master .
He isn 't home . He 'll be back late at night .
You can come back here tomorrow morning .
We 'll come back tomorrow then .
Should we call the horse driver to take us back ?
And return here tomorrow ? What a hassle .
There 's a pathway . I think someone must come here often .
That has to stop . We 'll have to make a huge sign saying , " Do Not Enter ! "
Dini , it 's so huge .
Yes , it 's really huge .
How long has it been abandoned ?
I don 't know .
How old were you when you moved to the city ?
According to my aunt , when I was five years old .
And you 're 25 now ?
So it has been empty for 20 years .
Who is that ?
I don 't know .
It seems this house was abandoned in a hurry .
What do you mean ?
All the furniture is still here .
Yes ! This still works .
Where are you going ?
To check the most important place in a house .
We 'll have to do lots of pumping tonight .
This is crazy , Maya !
This house and the land may be as big as 900 square meters !
Imagine how much money you 'd get if you sell it .
What are you doing ?
I found it in the drawer , still wrapped in a plastic bag .
Did your aunt keep any of the documents ?
Not that I know of .
I bet your dad also owned properties in other places .
We have to reclaim that property too .
This is crazy . You can be rich !
Don 't forget me , okay ?
Your parents are gorgeous .
You 're sad , aren 't you ?
No , I just don 't get it .
Why ?
I 'm not in any of these photos ,
only in the photo that I 've shown you .
Maybe they didn 't have a chance to take your photo .
There are piles of photos here . I 'm not in one of them .
Maybe you were an ugly kid ?
Just forget about it .
Okay ?
Maybe they preferred to kiss you rather than take photos of you .
Isn 't that better ?
I think someone just died and was buried .
Are you sure your parents were buried here ?
Where else would they be ?
But you said you think your folks left in a hurry .
You meant they had to leave the village , right ?
You might be right .
Let 's just finish this row , then we go back to the house .
Can we go back now ?
Dini , it 's just dead people . Why are you afraid of the graveyard ?
I 'm not scared . I just think it 's pointless .
Dead people should just be cremated . So they won 't take up space like this .
It 's better to turn the land into housing for the living .
Hey .
You have to promise me .
When I die , please cremate my body . And spread my ashes in the sea .
I might get reincarnated as a fish . It 's better than being a human .
You 'll get caught by fishermen and turned into sushi .
I 'll be a shark , and eat humans .
Sharks don 't eat humans .
Unless they 're really hungry .
Dini .
They 're here .
NYAI SHINTA
You 've seen their graves . Now let 's go .
Hold on .
Do you know the prayer for dead people ?
You 're asking me ?
Just say it in Indonesian . You think God only speaks Arabic ?
What did you pray for anyway ?
So that they rest in peace .
Did you pray so you can get their fortune ?
That too .
Good .
Maya .
Why are there so many children 's graves ?
Maybe they 're not children , just really tiny graves .
Just look at the dates .
CHILD OF WONSO-TUMINI COUPLE BORN AND DIED JULY 7TH , 2016
They didn 't even have names .
What is up with your village , Maya ?
HARJOSARI VILLAGE CEMETERY
CEMETERY COURTESY OF KI DONOWONGSO
It seems that the villagers don 't really like your family .
Dini !
What ?
Did you hear that ?
Yes .
I heard your annoying voice .
I 'm serious !
What do you want ? I 'm so tired , Maya !
How can you sleep in a dusty bed like this ?
Shut up .
- Dini . - Shut up .
Shit .
Dear Almighty .
Give me pain that I can bear .
What are you doing ?
I think someone just died .
Again ?
Maya , what are you doing ?
Within two days , two people have died .
No wonder this village seems empty .
Wait !
What should we do ?
Just be calm .
I heard that you came to my house to see me ?
That 's right , sir .
You 're writing a book about puppet masters ?
For our university , sir . We are university students .
Why did you choose this village ?
We 've visited other villages that are still performing wayang .
Then we heard about you . So we came here .
How old are the both of you ?
We 're 20 years old .
We are very sorry to come during an inconvenient time .
Don 't worry about it .
Come to my house if you want to talk .
Thank you , sir .
We need to leave this village now .
What ?
This place creeps me out . They look like they 're going to eat us alive .
And someone dies here daily .
- It 's just a coincidence . - No way .
If you 're desperate about your inheritance ,
we can send someone to come here and take care of it .
You think we can afford that ?
We 're broke . We can 't even pay rent this month .
We 'll figure something out . We always do .
Look , we 're here now . We just have to stay a little longer .
We may not have to spend another night .
We 'll ask Ki Saptadi if the house actually belongs to my family . Then , we go .
We have to ask him in a gentle manner .
Yes , a very gentle way .
I 'm not sure of this idea .
Come on , Dini . We can do this .
Maya , how are you going to ask him about the house
without revealing that you 're Rahayu ?
It 's risky . Someone tried to kill you , remember ?
And most likely because of the house .
Understood . So let 's just play along as students .
Nobody kills students .
Fine . I 'm going to go back to the house .
I stink like a dead raccoon . I want to shower .
Fine . I 'll find us something to eat .
Excuse me .
Can I buy some food ?
To eat here or to go ?
Two to go , please .
Two rice with egg and vegetables .
Miss .
Do you know anything about that big , abandoned house ?
Do you know who it belongs to ?
A family used to live there when I was still a child .
Who ?
It 's a house of evil .
What did she say ?
It 's full of diseases .
My grandmother said it 's a house of disease .
What does she mean ?
She said the devils used to live there and left a horrendous disease .
Can I help you ?
Excuse me , miss .
We heard that you and your friend spent a night here .
It 's not allowed .
So sorry , we couldn 't find another place .
This old house has been abandoned for a long time .
It 's not safe . The roof might cave in .
I know , thank you for your concern . We 're leaving soon .
I know it 's a pity a house this big is unoccupied .
But it doesn 't belong to us , so we can 't use it .
Who does it belong to ?
The heir of this family . A girl .
Ki Saptadi has all of the documents .
He has been waiting for the girl to claim it ,
so he can give back all of the documents .
So this house will no longer be his responsibility .
Is the girl 's name Rahayu ?
How do you know the name ?
Because ...
I am Rahayu .
Well , Ki Saptadi is about to go
to another village .
If you can meet him now , he can give you the documents .
Where 's your friend ?
She 's getting us something to eat .
She really is a college student . I 'm accompanying her .
Well , it 's up to you .
If you want to wait until Ki Saptadi is back , be my guest .
He 'll return ... in three days .
Three days ?
But earlier today , he told us to come to his house tonight ,
so my friend could ask him some questions for her research .
Yes , that was before .
But he got a sudden invitation to perform in another village .
And it 's quite far from here .
Okay , then . I 'll go meet him now .
We can take you to him .
I know where he lives .
Well , he is at a villager 's house . Not far from here .
Come , we 'll take you there .
Are we still far ?
Just a little bit more .
Why are we not taking the main road ?
It 's closer through here .
I think I 'd better get back . My friend is waiting for me .
What the hell ?
Listen .
You don 't have to rape me .
I 'm no virgin . All you have to do is ask .
Don 't cut her skin .
Why ?
Dini ?
I brought food , aren 't you hungry ?
The number you 're calling is not active or out of coverage area .
Please try again in a few minutes .
Please ... spare me .
What do you want ? !
Please let me go .
What should I do to be released ?
Sir ! Please help me , sir !
I don 't know what I did wrong .
If I ever wronged you , please forgive me , sir .
Rahayu ...
We 're ready , sir .
Mother .
Please help me , ma 'am !
What are you doing ?
There are two women who are headed into labor soon .
If we hurry , we might be able to save their babies .
I thought you weren 't coming .
Are you here for the interview ?
Actually , I 'm looking for my friend .
The one who was with me earlier when we met .
Is she not with you ?
I left to buy some food ,
but when I returned , she was gone .
I will ask someone to look for her .
You can wait for her here .
No need . I mean , thank you for your help ,
but I want to keep looking for her .
Very well . I pray for her safe return .
Thank you , sir .
You 're welcome .
Our baby is going to be all right .
Excuse me , miss .
You can watch from the other side , miss .
I want to ask Ki Saptadi if he has any information on my missing friend .
We 've looked for her everywhere , but we weren 't able to find her .
We 'll look again after this show is finished .
- All right . Thank you . - You 're welcome .
Please go that way .
The number you are calling is not active .
Where are you , Dini ?
A woman is going into labor , come and see .
Push . Come on , child . Yes , that 's it .
A little bit more . Come on , push .
Push .
That 's it . Just one more push . You can do it .
Sir .
No ...
You said my baby was going to be healthy .
You lied !
You 're a liar !
I 'm doing all I can
to help you and everybody in this village .
Damn you !
Will my baby ...
still be cursed ?
What are you doing here ?
I 'm just wandering around .
Go home .
I want to see the baby .
Just go home !
Come with me .
Don 't worry .
I 'm not like the others .
Come with me .
What 's going on in this village ?
What 's wrong with the babies ?
I will tell you everything later .
Come with me .
I have to find my friend .
I will help you look for her .
But you have to hide now .
It 's not safe .
Come . I live by myself .
Come in . Don 't worry .
My name is Ratih .
I 'm not a bad person .
The baby I saw ...
It 's cursed .
What ?
This whole village is damned .
- Please sit . - " Damned " ? In this day and age ?
Didn 't you notice anything peculiar about this village ?
Haven 't you noticed
there are no children here ?
I saw three girls last night .
That 's impossible .
There haven 't been any children in this village in 20 years .
What do you mean ?
There was once a very wealthy man in this village .
He was our village elder .
He and his family lived in that big , abandoned house .
They had many servants .
One of them was Nyi Misni , Ki Saptadi 's mother .
The village elder had a son .
His name was Ki Donowongso .
When his father died , Ki Donowongso inherited all the wealth .
He was not only rich ,
he was very good at making the wayang puppets
and a brilliant puppet master .
He was also famous among the neighboring villages .
Then there was Nyai Shinta , the most beautiful woman in the village .
All the men wished to be her husband .
In the end , Ki Donowongso and Nyai Shinta got married .
It was a huge wedding . The party lasted for seven days .
Unfortunately , after three years of marriage , they could not bear a child .
Nyai Shinta was depressed and ashamed .
Finally , after five years of trying ,
Nyai Shinta got pregnant .
Ki Donowongso took great care of his wife .
They held a party every Saturday night .
He would perform with his puppets all night long .
The odd thing is no one knew what happened to the baby after it was born .
No one ever saw the baby .
Why is that ?
The baby was born without skin .
Since then , Ki Donowongso refused to mingle with the villagers .
My daughter ...
Not long after that , a five-year-old girl in the village went missing .
She was never found .
Soon after that , two more girls went missing .
One day , the villagers saw Ki Donowongso 's baby for the first time .
She looked so healthy and beautiful .
It was only then that the village learned the baby was named Rahayu .
A rumor started to spread among the villagers ,
saying that Rahayu 's father had something to do with the three missing girls .
But no one dared to confront him .
Until one night ...
Ki Saptadi said that Ki Donowongso had been practicing black magic ,
making a pact with the devil to protect his daughter .
But then he went mad .
It was said
that a loyal servant took his daughter away to the city .
And ever since that day , the village has been cursed .
Every baby has been born without skin .
Why do they have to kill the babies ?
Because if they were allowed to live , they would be living in misery .
You don 't know that . Perhaps there is a cure .
No . There 's one baby who was allowed to live .
He now lives in the forest .
Uncured and in constant pain .
Ki Saptadi said that , in order to lift the curse ,
the first girl who got the disease , Rahayu , has to be skinned
and her skin has to be made into leather puppets .
Why do the villagers believe in Ki Saptadi 's words ?
Who else do we have to look up to here ?
Ki , is there anything else we should do ?
Did we miss something ?
We skinned the wrong girl !
Do you want to eat ?
No , thank you .
I 'll get you some rice , okay ?
Who 's that in the picture ?
My husband .
Everyone .
The woman we 've been looking for is here in this village .
- Yes ! - Yes !
- You know what she looks like . - Yes !
- You all know ? - Yes !
- Get her ! - Yes !
- Look for the woman ! - Yes !
- Block all the village 's exits . - Yes !
- The curse will be lifted soon ! - Yes !
Where is your husband now ?
He went to the city three months ago .
He was looking for a cure .
Cure for what ?
Can you feel that ?
My grandmother , whom you met at the kiosk , is a good shaman .
She said if someone made a pact with the devil ,
and a curse is born , it can never be reversed .
It 'll only transform into another curse .
That 's why I don 't believe that killing you
will lift the curse .
And that 's why I asked my husband to search for a cure in the city .
I believe he will be able to find it .
Did you see the woman from the city ?
" Woman from the city " ?
Yes , two of them came to our village .
One of them is Ki Donowongso 's daughter .
Ki Saptadi killed the other one . The wrong one .
They skinned her , turned her skin into leather puppets . What a waste .
What do you think you 're doing ?
You won 't share some food with your neighbors now ?
No . Please go .
Why are you so rude ?
Are you lonely because your husband has been away for a long time ?
Do you want me to stay with you tonight ?
How long since you 've seen a man 's erection ?
Get out !
Just stab me .
Or I 'll kill myself .
Then my ghost will haunt you for the rest of your life !
Jo !
Pigs !
Come on , miss .
Miss , I 'm so sorry about your friend .
I need to get out of here as soon as possible .
Stay here for a while . It 's still not safe .
They won 't come again .
We don 't know that .
At least if I run now , I have a chance .
Dini ...
Dini was my best friend .
This is all my fault .
No , it 's not .
It 's the work of the devil and weak humans .
Do you have a mobile phone ?
- Come on ! - Check it !
Hello ?
Miss ? I 'm with a police officer .
We 're on our way .
We 're taking a motorbike so it 's faster .
Thank you . I 'll be there .
They 're almost here .
She said to meet her at the North entrance .
I know where it is .
Then , can we drive faster ?
This is the fastest I can go .
I 've met your husband .
He tried to kill me .
I was working at night . He came and tried to kill me .
He was shot by the police and died .
Please forgive me , Ratih .
- Is this it ? - Yes , this is the North Entrance .
Suryo .
Good evening .
Bambang ?
I told you to stay put . I can handle this by myself .
We just want to help .
Who are you people ?
We 're from this village .
You know them ?
The thing is , I 'm from here too . Me and my wife .
Didn 't I tell you ?
No , you didn 't .
- Your name is ... - Nano .
Don 't worry , Mr. Nano . All the villagers are friendly .
- Give me your phone . - No .
- Just for a minute . - No !
You dare to fight a police officer ?
Damn you !
Over there !
Where is she ?
Find her !
Sir , help me . They want to rape me .
Get in !
I 'll ride in the back so they can 't see me .
Okay , hop on !
Help .
Find her !
Don 't let her get away !
You will forget .
The unborn shall perish .
Good morning , madam .
She must be here ! Find her ! Now !
Come on , she must be here !
Hurry , find her !
Don 't let her get away !
Blood for blood .
Hurry !
She has nowhere to run !
Bury our skin with our bones , and the curse will be gone .
Miss Maya !
Miss ! Wake up ! We have to get out of here . Come on !
What is that place ?
It 's where Tole lives , the cursed child who was kept alive .
I want to see him .
You have to go now .
Who 's there ?
It 's me . Ratih .
I 'm hungry ... I want to eat ...
Who is that , Ratih ?
I will be back with food .
It 's all my fault .
No , it 's not .
But I can make things right .
Why are you still helping me ?
Hating you will not change anything .
They will hurt you if they know you 're helping me .
They 've hurt me all my life .
Let 's just do what you want to do .
I will help .
What is that ?
The skin of the missing girls .
Your work here is done .
It 's better that you go now .
I 'm not going anywhere until I know that the curse is gone .
A woman is going into labor soon .
We 'll wait and see .
I used to live in this house .
This is where ...
Donowongso 's father
used to fuck me
until Saptadi finally was born in this house too .
Go see the woman who is in labor .
Please go , now !
I never told him
that Saptadi ...
was his illegitimate son .
I never asked him to take any responsibility for Saptadi .
I knew my place .
This is all your fault .
Even before I was born , you tried to kill me .
You started this curse .
You ...
are a mistake that I need to erase .
Just stay away for me , okay ?
Stay away from me !
Stay away !
Sir , please let me go .
Sir , please let me go home .
We have to do this .
Please understand .
Sir , everything is all right now .
There will be no more curse .
No more babies will be born without skin .
What ?
The three little girls , the ones that were never found ...
My father buried them inside the house .
In the basement . Their spirits came to me .
They asked me to bury the puppets that were made from their skin
in the same location where their bones were buried . So they can rest in peace .
I 've done everything that they asked me to do .
Go look . The puppets are gone from your house .
Please , sir ...
Please , sir . I 'm not lying .
I ...
Father ...
Please , I 'm your daughter .
What did you say ?
I 'm your daughter .
I know everything . I am your daughter .
Yours and Nyai Shinta 's .
Your mother put a spell on you to forget .
Don 't listen to her !
Grandmother , what have I done to deserve this ?
I 've been living in misery all my life .
You brought me into this world . Now you want to kill me .
Shut up !
Is this true , Mother ?
This is all your fault ?
- You dare to talk that way to your mother ? - Enough !
Enough already .
I 've had enough of you controlling my life .
Is it her , or your mother ?
My wife 's in labor . What should we do ?
Choose her , or me !
Father ?
The baby 's healthy !
Please ...
My dear ?
- My dear ... - Give me back my baby !
Please .
You have to die .
Our child .
You have to go now .
Come with me , Ratih .
It doesn 't matter where I go , my life will be the same .
Go !
Go now !
Hurry ! Go !
ONE YEAR LATER
The baby is healthy .
Of course he is .
He keeps kicking me .
Maybe he hates his father .
Of course he hates you .
He knows you knocked me up and are putting me through a hard time .
Hold on . I have to pee . Just a moment .
This is what happens to pregnant women .
Be careful .
What happened ?
What happened to the baby ?
Where 's the baby ?
How did this happen ?
Why ?